你已经把你的创业想法跟我说过无数次了
You've told me about your start-up idea over a 100 times now.
你着手去做了吗？
Why don't you do something about it?
我怎样才能融到钱，巴蒂？
How will I get the funding, Bhati?
不是每个人的运气都像你那么好
Everyone's luck isn't as good as your's.
你是什么？
What are you?
什么意思？
What do you mean
你是啤酒
You are a beer.
我现在就辞职
I will resign right now.
我的B计划会被选中吗？
My B-Plan is going to get selected?
你应该...-永不放弃
You should... -never quit
伙计们
Guys!!!
我放弃了
I quit!!!
开始创业吧
Now let's just begin with the start-up
我们三年前就开始讨论这个问题了-纳文，我们已经讨论过这个问题了
We've only been talking about it since 3rd year. -Naveen we've already discussed this.
一年半之后，等你从巴西回来的时候
That by the time you come back from Brazil, after a
year and a half, Yogi will make some contacts here.
尤吉将在这里建立一些关系
理解我一下，我现在不能辞职
Guys try to understand, I can't leave my job right now.
大家开始意识到我的潜力
People are realizing my potential.
我是公司的重要员工
I’m a valuable employee to the company.
听我说
Listen to me.
一个新的硅谷正在这里崛起
A new Silicon Valley is being upstaged at Hiranandani here!
而你却还在用 Python 写代码
And you're still writing codes on Python.
每当这个国家的毕业生厌倦了朝九晚五的工作..
Whenever graduates of this country, get bored by their 9 to 5 jobs...
为了摆脱困境，他们只有三个选择
So, to get out, they come up with only three options for themselves.
读MBA
MBA
读IAS
IAS
或者去创业
or Start-Up.
北京
Beijing.
我们准备开始在那里扩张，比原计划提前了6个月
We're beginning our expansion there, 6 months ahead of schedule.
一周内有个会议
Apointment within a week.
我们需要一个聪明人
We need someone smart over there...
像你一样
Like you.
现在才是真正的选择
Now is the real choice.
已经得到的一定比不确定的更好
One in hand is obviously better than one not-so-sure in the bush.
是纳文让我来这儿的
He's the one who requested me to come here.
他..
He...
不得不马上离开
... had to leave urgently.
让我用啤酒再给你们讲一遍
Let me explain it to you, with beer today.
它不会烫伤你，只会洒出来
It won't burn, even if it spills.
你回来了
You're back!!!
我就知道你会来的
I knew it, you'd come!
阿克希尔给我们坑了
Akhil gave us the wrong information!
我们的名字不在获胜者名单上
Our name's not on the winner's list!
但是等等..
But wait...
现在我的薪水怎么办？
What about my salary now?
如果你不能用两块披萨喂饱你的团队，说明团队人太多了
妈妈! 我不想结婚
MOM! I don't want to get married!!!
我才27岁，还没到结婚的年龄
I'm only 27. Not even old enough to get married!
不要叫我尚娜·贝塔
Don't "Shona beta" me!
妈妈... 妈妈，别对我撒谎，好吗？
Mummy... Mummy, don't lie to me, OK?
你没有得甲状腺癌
You don't have any Thyroid cancer!
好的，等等... 我接到另一个电话
OK wait... I'm getting another call.
是的... 等等! 等等
Yeah... Wait! Wait!
喂？是阿尔蒂吗？
Yeah Aarti?
实际上还没有，我还在开会
Actually no. I'm still in a client meeting.
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
哦，你已经到了？
Oh, you've already reached?
在哪里？
Where?
好的好的
OK. OK.
这么说你已经到了？
You've just reached, then?
不不不..
No, no, no...
我的会议... 可以取消
My client meeting... can be cancelled!
是的，我在路上了
Yeah, I'm on my way!
我们走
Let's go.
我们随便绕一圈再回来
We've to go around and then come back here!
快点
Come on!
开车啊
Come on already!
嗨
Hi!
对不起，我来晚了
Sorry, I got a little late.
希望我没有让你等太久
Hope I didn't keep you waiting for long!
不
No!
气氛不错
Nice ambience!
你点了什么吗？
Did you order anything?
两杯卡布奇诺
Akhilesh, 2 cappuccinos!
不... 我什么都不想要
No... I don't want to have anything!
不不……我自己喝两杯
No, no. Both are for me.
我现在喝一杯，另一杯等凉了再喝
I'll drink one now, and the other one later, once it gets cold.
在这点冰咖啡要额外收一百块
These guys charge 100 bucks extra for cold coffee!
顺便说一句
By the way...
你看起来..
You look...
和你的照片完全不同
Quite different from your pictures!
我知道
I know!
我不上相
I'm not photogenic!
我是说..
I mean...
我在现实生活中看起来还不错
I look good in real life!
但是我的照片，照出来效果不是很好
But my pictures, don't come out that great!
你以前约过吗？
You've met guys before... like this?
嗯
Yes!
两三次吧
2-3 times
我也约过
Me too!
六次
6 times!!!
你知道..
You know...
自从我从印度管理学院毕业之后
Since I've completed my P.G. from IIM Indore?
我妈让姑娘们排队等着我去见她们
Mom's had girls lined up for me to meet!
我告诉她”妈妈..
I told her, "Mom...
我现在不能结婚
...I can't marry right now!...
我想探索这个世界……
...I want to explore the world...
和朋友一起旅行……
...Travel with friends...
... 潜水..
...Scuba dive...
滑翔"
...Sky dive"
我告诉你... 你也应该停止这种行为
I'm telling you... You too should stop with this marraige shabang!
婚姻根本毫无意义
Marriage doesn't even make sense
像我们这样的年轻人应该玩得开心
Youngsters like us should have fun!
但我觉得我妈强迫我注册账号是好事
It's a good thing actually, that my mom forcefully made me a profie.
否则，我们就不会有今天的约会了
Or else, we wouldn't have been on this date!
等一下
Wait a minute!
你妈妈... 让你..
Your mom... made your...
注册约炮软件？
Tinder profile?
约炮？
Tinder?
不，不，是 shaadi. com
No, no. Shaadi.com
你是..
You're..
嗨
Hi.
尼基塔？
Nikita?
尼基塔
Nikita.
尼基塔？
Nikita?
尼基塔
Nikita.
哦..
Oh...
哦，糟了……
Oh shit... shit!
抱歉抱歉
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
我有点懵逼
I got confused!
幸好他提前来了
It's a good thing he showed up early!
我们就要……
We were about to get...
我们就要结婚了
WE were about to get married!
索拉布 · 曼达尔
Saurabh Mandal!
我是科技公司的市场主管
I'm a marketing head in Technity.
你是做什么的？
And what do you do?
今天是星期四？
Today's Thursday?
是的
Yes.
星期四我..
On Thursdays I...
练腿
...do legs!
健身房
Gym!!!
不错... 不错
Nice... Nice
请坐! 你们聊
Please have a seat! Enjoy!
你们聊
Enjoy!
玩得开心
And have fun also.
索拉布先生？
Mr. Saurabh?
阿蒂？
Aarti?
是这样，阿蒂，我想在开始之前先澄清一些事情
Actually, Aarti. I wanted to clear something first, before we start.
索拉布先生，我知道你想说什么
Mr. Saurabh, I know what you want to say.
你以前有过女朋友，是吗？
That you've had girlfriends before this, isn't it?
我知道
I know.
不是，不是这样的
No, not really. That's not it.
你怎么知道我喜欢卡布奇诺？
How did you know that I like cappuccino?
阿蒂，听着..
Aarti, look...
我一开始就不想来这里
I didn't want to come here in the first place
我妈逼我来的
It's just that my mom wanted me to be here.
父母逼婚，你懂的
You know how parents pressurize you
你的..
Your...
你的小胡子和阿尼尔·卡普尔的一模一样
Your moustache is just like Anil Kapoor's!
不，阿蒂..
No look, Aarti...
事实上，我不能跟你结婚
Actually, I can't go ahead with this marriage!
索拉布先生，我理解你的不情愿
Mr. Saurabh, I understand your reluctance!
你要多少糖
How much sugar?
一包
One.
跟我一样
Just like me!
跟你说实话吧
Look, if I were to tell you the truth...
在这之前我也有过两个男朋友
I too, had two boyfriends before this
而且我和他们也很亲密
And I got intimate with them, as well!
但我们没有做任何“肮脏”的事情
But we didn't do anything "dirty".
我只会……
That I will do...
和我的丈夫做
...only with my husband.
毕竟，我是一个印度人
After all, I'm an Indian!
我怎么能忘本呢
How can I forget my roots and culture
阿蒂，毫无疑问，你是个很好的女孩..
Aarti. No doubt, you're a very nice girl...
潘迪先生也是这么说的
Panditji too, says the same
不，不，现在..
No, no. Now...
我..
Now, I...
索拉布先生，我同意了
Mr. Saurabh, it's a yes for me.
只是..
Just...
别像上一个家伙..
Like the last guy...
不要对我隐瞒任何事
Don't hide anything from me!
为什么... 他隐瞒了什么？
Why... What did the last one hide?
我和他的婚事已经确定了……
My marriage with him had been confirmed.
但就在订婚前几天..
But just a few days before the engagement...
我爸爸知道了
...dad got to know that...
他辞掉了一份稳定的工作，准备开始创业
...he was quitting a stable job to begin a start-up!
然后我们的婚事就此结束了
And the marriage got canned, then and there.
后来我就看到了你的资料
That's when I saw your profile and...
就算他要创业又怎样
So what, if he was going to begin a start-up?
为什么女孩要嫁给创业者？
Why would any girl marry a "start-up guy"?
现在这个时代... 如果公司做得不好..
Now... If the company doesn't do well...
我难道要放下家务出门工作吗？
Will I have to leave my household chores and go do a job?
你说呢，索拉布先生？
Tell me Mr. Saurabh?
实际上，阿蒂
Actually, Aarti...
这正是我想告诉你的..
This is exactly, what I wanted to tell you about...
从明天开始自己洗衣服
No laundry from tomorrow!
告别保洁阿姨
No maid from tomorrow!
告别牛奶
No milk from tomorrow!
连报纸都要告别
Even, no newspaper from tomorrow!
告别健身房会员
Gym membership will be cancelled!
出门坐地铁
Metros will be used instead of the car!
节约用电
Electricity will be saved!
宽带从8mbps 降低到1mbps
Internet speed will be reduced from 8mbps to 1mbps!
别啊，兄弟
No. No. No. No dude.
宽带就别降了
Atleast let the net speed stay!
难道你不想要杰图了吗？
Do you not want Jeetu, then?
如果我们存的钱不够，怎么保证他的工资呢？
If we don't save enough, how will we ensure his salary?
好吧，让我们把速度从8mbps 降低到4mbps
Alright then. Let's reduce the speed from 8mbps to 4mbps.
付费电视停掉
Table top-ups will be stopped!
外卖停掉
Ordering food from restaurants will be stopped!
绝对要停
Will be absolutely stopped!
实际上，任何奢侈消费都要停
Infact, all kinds of luxury expenditures will be absolutely stopped!
现在有多少了
What's the total?
三千
Three thousand
七百
Seven hundred
二十五
Twenty-five.
再加上我的份额..
And adding my share to it...
七千
Seven thousand
四百
Four hundred
五十
Fifty.
杰图的工资是多少？
And how much is Jeetu's salary?
一个月
One lac
三万七千
Thirty seven thousand
五百
Five hundred.
好计划
Superb plan!
我们可以存一年半的钱
We'll save for a year and a half...
支付一个月的薪水
...and shell out one month's salary!
“欧耶! ”
"Alright!"
曼达尔，你在干什么
Madal, what are you doing dude?
什么？
What?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
音乐
Music!
吵闹的音乐
Loud music!
什么都听不见
Can't hear a thing!
你继续干吧
You carrry on!
“欧耶! ”
"Alright!"
我想说的是..
What I'm saying is...
我们再加50块..
Let's add another 50 bucks to this...
找几个实习生来写代码
And hire some intern to do the coding.
尤吉，实习生能替代杰图吗？
Yogi, an intern will replace Jeetu, now?
我们公司需要有工作经验的人
We need people with some work experience in our compnay!
在高层工作过的人
People who've worked at some senior level!
能组建团队的人
Someone who can build a team in the future...
能够制定战略的人
Someone who can strategize!
纳文..
Naveen...
你找到我的那件 t 恤了吗？
Did you find that t-shirt of mine?
什么 t 恤？
What t-shirt?
‘ InfoCom’那个
The 'InfoCom' one.
我在那里工作了四年
Where I'd an experience of 4 years?
作为高级顾问
As a Senior Consultant!
因为我组建了一个团队..
Since I'd BUILT a team there...
他们把那件 t 恤送给了我
They'd gifted that t-shirt to me.
我不知道，我们现在很忙
I don't know dude. We're busy right now!
妈的
Shit!
现在我得想想该穿什么了
Now, I'll have to strategize what to wear!
那我们该怎么办？
What do we do then?
伙计，我觉得我们卡在这了
Dude, I think we're getting a little impatient here!
我在想如果..
I was thinking, what if...
杰图设法说服了桑亚
Jeetu manages to convince Soumya!
纳文..
Naveen...
那是他的妻子
She's his wife!
她能跟他上床
She gives him sex!
你永远不能说服一个能跟你上床的女人
You can never convince a woman who gives you sex!
相信我
Trust me.
这都是经验之谈
This is all coming from experience!
听着，尤吉……
Look Yogi...
没有杰图，就没有公司
Without Jeetu, we have no company.
纳文..
Naveen...
我们现在没有工作
We've no jobs.
不管有没有杰图，我们都得开一家公司
We have to start a company, with or without Jeetu.
尤吉……
Yogi...
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
你有没有考虑好？
Did you think about it?
我昨天问了你什么？
I'd asked you something, yesterday?
你问了什么？
What'd you asked?
那个事……
That thing...
我能加入你们的创业吗？
Can I be part of your start-up?
什么？
WHAT?
为什么？
WHY?
你说“为什么”是什么意思？
What do you mean by "Why?"?
你们都是工程师
You all are engineers!
你需要一个有MBA的人
You need an MBA!
如果没有商业专长，你们如何经营一家公司？
How will you'll run a company without business expertise?
曼达尔，我还没考虑好
Mandal, I'll let you know!
给我点时间
Give me some time.
这是一个非常重要的职业决定
It's a very important professional decision!
我会告诉你的，好吗?-好的
I'll let you know, alright? -OK
那么你会给我发邮件，还是口头交流？
So will you send me a mail, or you'll communicate verbally?
我能在星期五之前接到电话吗？
Should I expect a call by Friday?
我会..
I'll...
等星期五干什么? 真是个可爱的孩子
Why Friday? He's a sweet kid!
今天就让我们来给你面试吧
Let's do your G.D. and P.I. today itself!
明天揭晓结果
And the results tomorrow.
今天面试？
Personal interview, today?
已经10点了，我什么时候准备... ..
Iit's already 10. When will I prepare...
妈的，已经10点了？
Fuck, it's 10 already?
要死要死要死
I'm going to get killed!
10点怎么了？
What if it's 10?
‘ Jhalak’只在晚上10点出现
'Jhalak' comes up only at 10 in the night!
不行，尤吉! 我得去见史瑞雅，如果我迟到了，她会整死我的
No Yogi! I've to meet Shreya. If I get late, she'll screw me!
你不是已经告诉她我们的创业的事了吗？
Haven't you told her already, about our start-up?
我都好几天没见她了
Where have I met her, since so many days?
曼达尔
MANDAL!
我的洗面奶呢？
Where's my face-wash dude?
那个库鲁勒本草洗面奶？
The 'Kurule' medical therapy one?
别用那个
Don't use that!
我用了之后它和我的四个粉刺结合成一个疖子
I used it and 4 of my pimples combined into a boil!
不是，我的洗面奶
No dude. My face-wash!
你要去找洗面奶吗？还是我们应该在面试前取消你的资格？
Will you get it, or should we disqualify you before the interview round, itself?
我正要去呢
I was just about to go!
听着..
Dude, look...
有个程序员..
There's this coder...
他才大三
He's in the third year.
他是我一个朋友的叔叔的儿子
He's the son of the paternal uncle of a mutual friend!
他就像是我的家人
He's almost family!
我们带上他吧，我向你保证，他会很棒的
Let's get him onboard. I assure you, he'll rock!
听着，尤吉
Look, Yogi!
公司的一切都在于人
A comapny's all about the people in it.
你认为，任何一个大学生都可以取代杰图
You think, any college guy can replace Jeetu...
如果我们这样随机招人，那为什么我们不雇佣曼达尔呢？
If that's how randomly we want to hire people, why don't we hire Mandal as well?
对不起，打扰了你的重要会议
Sorry to disturb your important meeting!
但是我希望你能做出正确的决定
But I hope you take the right decision!
我也很看好杰图
I also love Jeetu!
虽然已经过去三年了，我当年还是抄他的答题卡毕业的
Though 3 years late, I've passed by cheating from his answer sheet.
我当然希望他能加入
We definitely want him onboard.
但目前我们不能满足他的工资，而且急需一个程序员
But till the time we do not ensure his salary, we need a coder.
我告诉你..
I'm telling you...
我们去见见这个家伙..
Let's go meet this guy...
然后就开始干吧
And let's get the fucking thing started!
好吧
OK, alright.
现在我先去见史瑞雅
Let me meet Shreya for now.
然后，我们下午去见那个家伙，好吗？
After that, let's go meet this guy, in the afternoon. OK?
我看起来怎么样？
How do I look?
还行
Fair!
好吧，借过，我去找史瑞雅，然后再联系你
OK. You make a move, I'll go meet Shreya and then catch you!
走走走走
Go. Go. Go. Go.
喂？
Hello?
纳文-嗨，史瑞雅
Naveen!!! - Hey Shreya!
你还没有升级你的宽带，对不对
You still haven't upgraded your internet, have you?
近来可好？
How are you?
你真是个守财奴，一辈子守财奴
You've always been and always will be a miser!
你能看见我吗？
Can you see me?
等一下
Wait a second.
你能看见我？
You can see me?
我现在能看见你了
I can see you now.
天啊，你穿的那是件什么衬衫？
Oh God, what is that shirt you're wearing?
你是从园丁那里借的吗？
Have you borrowed it from the gardenkeeper?
事实上，他的和我的衬衫尺寸是一样的，所以很适合我
Actually, his and mine shirt size is the same. So it fit me!
顺便说一下，他的妻子穿XL看起来也是这样，会适合你
By the way, his wife wears XL. Looks like that too, will fit you!
要是你有什么是XL号的就好了，不是吗？
If only you had something XL, no?
宝贝，我有我的心
Baby, I have my heart.
我的心是如此的宽广
My heart is so big.
好吧，你应该知道，我一直在不丹寻找WiFi信号
OK, you should know, that I haven't been looking for
来听你这些废话
wi-fi all over Bhutan, to listen to all these ridicules.
是啊，好像是我要你去不丹似的
Yeah, as if I asked to go to Bhutan!
学习冥想，咨询项目只是一个借口
Meditation is being learnt, with Consultancy Project only as an excuse.
如果你想学冥想，你完全可以……
If it's meditation that you wanted to learn, you could've done that
每天早上醒来看电视上的《拉姆德夫巴巴》
just by waking up in the mornings to watch 'Ramdev baba' on the T.V.
对，我就喜欢看那些毛茸茸的老男人在早上6点汗流浃背
Yeah, because I just love old, hairy men sweating at 6 in the morning!
你以为我为什么要和你上床，宝贝？
Why do you think I sleep with you, baby?
宝贝，我认为你和我上床是因为
Baby, I thought you sleep with me, because not
你在做慈善，不是吗？
a lot of men, believe in doing charity, no?
你想让我开始数做慈善的数量吗？
Oh, you want me to start counting down on the charity cases?
我们是不是应该数数你的约会史?-不不不不..
Should we start listing your dating history, now? -No, no, no, no...
什么时候我的真爱，撕开云彩..
When is my true love, by tearing through clouds...
降落在这个我们称之为印度的土地上
Landing on the grounds of this country, we call India!
四点钟
Four O'clock!
四点整
Sharp!
你会来接我的，对吧？
You're coming to get me, right?
好的，我8点有个会议，我有很重要的事情要告诉你
Ok, I've a meeting at 8 and I've something very important to tell you.
哦! 我也有很重要的事要告诉你
Oh! Even I've something very important to tell you.
好吧，我先说，求求你，求求你，让我先说
OK, I'll go first. Please. Please. Let me go first!
好吧，去吧，好像我还有得选似的
OK, go. As if I have a choice.
说吧
Blurt out!
是这样的……
Actually...
纳文，我怀孕了
Naveen, I'm pregnant.
非常好
Very nice!
是谁的孩子？
Who's child is it?
我不知道..
I don't know...
谁都有可能
It could be anyone's.
可能是你的
It could be yours.
可能是拉哈夫的，也可能是瓦伊巴夫的
It could be Raghav's. It could be Vaibhav's.
哦，甚至可能是那个修道士的
Oh, it could even be the monastery monk's.
你有什么重要的话要说，还是你只是在浪费我流量
Do you have anything important to say or are you just eating into my internet pack?
不不不我确实有重要的事情要说
No. No. No. I do have something important to say.
但是我想要你一个惊喜
But I'd thought, that I'd keep it a surprise.
我应该告诉你吗？
Should I tell you?
什么? 你买了手铐？
What? You bought handcuffs?
是的，但除此之外..
Yeah, but apart from that...
是这样的
So!
有个人，他要离开他的女朋友去巴西
There's this guy, who's leaving his girlfriend and moving to Brazil.
这个女孩，决定开始找工作
This girl, decides to start looking for a job.
在巴西
In Brazil.
还有，你猜怎么着？
And, guess what?
她发现自己进入了最后的候选名单
She finds herself in the final shortlist.
史瑞雅! 等等
Shreya! Wait!
只差一次电话面试了，在那之后……
...last telephonic interview is left, but after that...
史瑞雅，等等
Shreya, wait.
- 她就跟你一起在里约生活了!-等等等等
...going to live with you in Rio, bitch! - Wait. Wait. Wait.
等等，史瑞雅
Wait Shreya...
这正是我想告诉你的消息
This is exactly what I wanted to give you news about.
告诉我
Tell me.
呃..
Uh...
你在干什么..
What are you doing...
我正要洗呢
I was just about to wash them up
你还要干多少活
How much will you work, after all!
洗衣机坏了，佣人也没来..
Anyway, the machine isn't workiing and the maid hasn't come...
没用多长时间……
It hardly takes time...
洗衣服……
I washed them...
怎么回事? 你今天突然..
What's the deal? Suddenly today...
不是突然吧
It isn't really "suddenly"!
我前天做了鸡肉
I'd cooked chicken, day before!
昨晚，我切的菜
And last night, I'd chopped the vegetables.
在一个家庭中，如果两个人一起做事，就没那么累了
In a household, if 2 people work in unison, it becomes easy.
现在有了各种各样的机器……
These days, these machines have come up...
否则..
Otherwise...
我们的父辈以前都是用手做的
Our dads used to do it all, by hands.
你怎么不去..
Why don't you go...
去祈祷吧，等我做完这里的事，我就去泡茶
Go do your prayers. I'll come, make tea, once I'm done here.
你有什么事要跟我说的吗？
Do you have something, to tell me?
没有啊
No!
你为什么这么想？
Why would you think so?
给我
Give me.
纳文... 给我打电话..
Naveen... had called...
尤吉和纳文已经辞职了
Yogi and Naveen have quit their jobs...
准备开始创业
They're going to begin their own start-up...
他们问了我……要不要一起
They were asking me... as well
你下楼去吧，我来搞定
You go on downstairs. I'll get done here.
你刚才说什么？
So what were you saying?
我刚才说什么来着..
What was I saying...
哦对……
No...
纳文和其他人问了我
Naveen and the guys were asking me as well...
要不要辞掉工作，加入他们的公司做CTO
To quit my job and join them as the C.T.O.
但是现在..
But now...
这... 你什么时候买的？
This... When did you buy this?
这是旧的
This is an old one!
从我父母那来的
Had gotten it from my parents'.
不... ... 我是说... ... 这颜色很适合你... ... 很好看
No... I was saying... These colors suit you... They come out very well!
那你怎么说？
So what did you say?
我说，我会考虑的... 现在这事情..
I said, I'll think about it... Now things like...
不能一下子就决定了
...these can't just be decided in the moment.
所以我也想和你谈谈这个
So I wanted to talk to you as well, about this.
这对你的职业发展有益吗
Will you be benefited, in your career?
如果初创企业发展壮大，那么是有好处的
If the start-up goes big, then there's a benefit...
否则，这就只是在冒险
Otherwise, it's just a risk!
工作会很有趣
Well, the work will be a lot of fun...
一定会很有趣的，但是薪水..
It'll be interesting but the salary...
我认为你应该去
I think you should do it.
什么？
What?
你搞错了
You're not doing it right...
给我
Give it to me!
不是……
No...
你刚才说什么？
What were you saying?
我认为，你应该去创业
I think, you should do it.
哈？
No...
真的没问题吗？
You don't have any problem?
我是想说……
I was trying to say, that once...
如果我辞职了，我们买房子的计划就要推迟了
...I quit my job, our plan to buy a house will be delayed.
为什么要急着买房子呢？
So, what's the hurry in buying a house?
不管怎么说，现在这房子也不错
Anyway, this is such a nice house.
这么大的阳台
There's such a big terrace!
而且你成长的机会，也会更多
And then the chances of your growth, are also so much more.
我连自助餐都没有
I won't even get an L.T.A.
我们也不得不取消毛里求斯之旅
We'll have to drop our Mauritius trip, as well.
我们还是去马哈巴莱斯赫瓦尔吧
We'll go to Mahabaleshwar, instead.
沙利尼的丈夫有一个度假村在那
Shalini's husband owns a resort there.
但薪水问题仍然是个问题
But the salary issue will still persist.
我们的储蓄足够了
Our savings are good enough.
不管怎样，我来孟买已经5个月了
Anyway, it's been 5 months since I've come to Mumbai.
我在想..
I'm thinking...
要出去找份工作
...of getting a good job for myself.
这些是怎么挂的? 用夹子吗？
How do you hang these? By clips?
我还以为你不会同意呢
I thought, you wouldn't agree to this.
我甚至还准备了流程图，用来说服你
I even had my flowcharts ready, so that I could convince you!
我从星期一开始就一直在想这个问题
I've only been thinking about this, since Monday.
所有的努力都白费了
All the effort, went waste!
别担心
Don't worry.
你的努力不会白费
None of your effort will go waste.
不管怎样..
Anyway...
你还得和你爸爸谈谈..
You'll have to talk to your dad about this...
你不会不问他就辞职吧？
You wouldn't quit your job, without asking him, would you?
拜托你做事靠谱一些好不好
I was asking you to do it properly!
现在我又得洗衣服了，全都要重洗
Now I'll have to wash, all the clothes again!
佣人今天都没来
Even the maid's not come today!
撤下所有的讲座然后换成色情视频
...got down all the lectures, and uploaded youporn videos, instead.
这小伙子赢了 IBM 代码竞赛两次以上..
Our guy's won the IBM code competition, twice over...
还是连续的
...in a row.
据说他收到了埃里克 · 施密特的祝贺信
Legend says that he got a congratulatory mail from Eric Schmidt, himself.
但是他没有随机的期望，不是吗？
But he doesn't have random expectations, does he?
他知道除了基本生活津贴他什么都拿不到对吧？
He knows, he won't get anything more than the basic stipend, right?
放松点! 他是自己人
Dude, relax! He's our kid!
我们请他吃几顿烧烤，他就会答应的
We'll offer him a couple of treats at Barbeque Nation and he'll say yes!
我告诉他，这是一个环境科学讲座，狗娘养的..
I told him, it's an Environment Science lecture motherf**ker...
如果不是代理，我是不是该打你屁股？
If not proxy, should I whoop your arse?
罗汉·奈吉的房间在这边吗？
Is Rohan Negi's room this way?
他在等你吗？
Is he expecting you?
是的
Yes.
跟我来
Follow me!
你去死吧
You go to hell!
我不想再见到你
I don't want to see your face again!
你不满足于只有前戏，是吗？
You aren't satisfied only with foreplay, are you?
你还得有个后续
You have to have this afterplay of melodrama!
她生气了，因为那是草莓味的
She got mad because it was strawberry.
只有杏仁或者开心果，而不是冰淇淋
It isn't ice-cream that you'd get almond and pistachio flavours!
叔叔们，有火柴吗？
Does the uncle party, have matchsticks?
快去食堂，时间到了
Go run to the canteen. It's time!
叔叔，给他一百块钱
Uncle, give him a 100 bucks.
掏钱
Give it.
跟我来
Follow me!
我不能再往前走了
I can't go beyond this point.
把你的手机、U盘和硬盘等等任何储存设备都拿出来
Deposit your mobiles, pendrives, hard-disks and any other storage devices.
前面那扇门
There's a door ahead...
敲门
Knock it.
敲两下
Twice!
然后等着
And then wait.
你们抽烟吗？
Do you smoke?
不抽
No.
辣鸡
Kids!
什么事？
Yes?
告诉钦图，尤吉·拜亚来了，给他一个实习机会
Tell chintu, that 'Yogi bhaiyaa' is here, to give him an internship.
进来吧
Come in.
坐
Sit.
他正在忙..
He's in the middle of something...
给他75
Give him 75.
分钟？
Minutes?
爆头数
Headshots!
尽管我是班长，但我从6年级到12年级的成绩稳步提高..
Despite being the class monitor, my performance from class 6 to class 12 steadily increased...
由72.3% 增加至87.8%
From 72.3% to 87.8%
这表明..
This goes to show...
我有责任..
I'm responsible...
坚持不懈
...persistent...
... 专注，积极，超越..
...dedicated, motivated, over...
被低估……
Under-rated dude!
有责任心，坚持不懈，积极主动，敬业乐业
Responsible, persistent, motivated, dedicated, under...
嗨，史瑞雅
Hi Shreya!
嗨，曼达尔
Hi Mandal!
嗨..
Hi...
对不起，我不是有意打扰你幻想幻灯片的
Sorry, I didn't mean to disturb your paranormal powerpoint fantasy.
我会偷偷溜进纳文的房间然后锁上门，这样你就不能进来了
I'll just sneak into Naveen's room and lock the door, so you can't come in!
不不不
No. No. No.
事实上，我是在等你
Actually, I was waiting for you!
纳文告诉我你会来
Naveen'd told me that you're going to come.
穿着那件运动夹克和毛巾？
In that blazer and towel?
你不是连环杀手曼达尔吧？
You aren't a serial killer Mandal, are you?
只有外表能杀人
Only, if looks could kill!
请坐
Please have a seat!
事实上，如果我感到紧张，我要去洗个澡
Actually, if I get tensed, I need to have a bath!
好点了吗？
Better?
恭喜你，曼达尔
Congratulations Mandal.
你已经到了令人毛骨悚然的新境界
You've reached a new level of creepy!
那么……
Soo...
纳文辞职去..
Naveen's quit his job to...
我知道，他什么都告诉我了
Yeah, I know. He's told me everything.
我也想..
And I too, want to...
所有的一切
Everything!
那么……
Soo...
那又怎样？
So?
史瑞雅，我们是朋友，对吧？
Shreya. We're friends, aren't we?
在 facebook 上还是在现实生活中？
Facebook-wise or in real life?
别闹
Joke!
你还记得吗？
Do you remember?
上个月，某个清晨..
Last month, early morning...
你想复印你的 PAN 卡
You wanted a Xerox of your PAN card.
纳文正在睡觉
Naveen was sleeping.
所以你找我帮忙
So you asked me for help.
我上班要迟到了..
I was getting late for work...
我身上没带零钱
I didn't have any change on me...
但我还是去把复印机弄好了
I still went and got the Xerox done.
听着，我有一个哲学理论
Look, I've this one philosophy...
朋友应该互相帮助
Friends should always help each other!
不不不不不
No. No. No. No. No.
等一下
One second.
你想让我说服纳文带你创业？
You want me to convince Naveen to hire you?
不行
No.
对不起
Sorry.
想都不要想
Not gonna happen.
不管怎样，我不能说服他，相反，他最终会说服我
Anyway, I can't convince him. Instead, he'll end up convincing me!
史瑞雅... 相信我
Shreya... Trust me!
他绝对不能说服你
He can never convince you!
男人永远都不能说服给了他……
A man can never convince a woman, who gives him...
... 爱的女人
...Love!
如果..
And if...
他不动摇的话……
He doesn't budge...
你知道..
You know...
用你的方法……
Use your methods!
什么方法？
What methods?
性交
Intercourse
什么？
What?
曼达尔，你疯了吗？
Mandal, have you gone nuts?
那个只要1块钱的复印机..
Just for a 1 buck Xerox...
实际上是两块钱，要复印两面呢
It's actually 2 bucks. One for each side!
我的价值远不止这些
I'm worth much more than that!
好吗? 对不起
OK? I'm sorry.
我可以帮你做其他的事情，但是这件事，我做不到! 对不起
I would've helped you with anything else, but with this, I can't! Sorry.
纳文需要我的帮助
Naveen needs my help!
尤吉一直从中作梗不让我加入
Yogi keeps winding him up against me!
我真的很想成为其中的一员
I really want to be a part of this!
我知道，我一定会后悔的
I know, I'm gonna regret this.
好吧
OK.
Alright.
我要确认一件事
Tell me one thing.
你会在什么时候……
When do...
叫水管工？
You call for a plumber?
那不是我..
That wasn't me...
纳文以为我弄坏了他的喷雾然后..
Naveen thinks that I broke his jet spray and then...
不，我是说假设
No. I mean hypothetically.
我是说..
I mean...
什么时候会有人叫水管工？
When would anyone, call for a plumber?
水龙头坏了，就叫水管工来
One calls for the plumber when a tap's broken.
对，如果水龙头没坏呢？
Right. And what if a tap isn't broken?
那为什么要叫水管工？
Then why call the plumber?
没错
Exactly!
你看
Look.
在这种情况下..
In this situation...
你是水管工，但纳文的公司并没有坏掉的水龙头
You're the plumber and Naveen's start-up doesn't have any broken tap.
无论你在生活中所做的贡献有多么伟大
Irrespective of, however great, the work you're doing in life is...
除非你的加入能解决他们的问题..
Unless, your inclusion doesn't solve any of their problems...
否则他们就不会需要你
They don't need you!
你要弄清楚他们需要什么
See... You need to figure out what they need.
你还需要一条更大的毛巾
You also need a bigger towel, dude!
别走
No. No.
不要回避
Don't shy away!
我穿着内裤呢
I'm wearing my underwear!
对不起
Sorry.
没穿
Not wearing any!
干你娘
F**K!
去你丫的
尤吉
Yogi!
还有..
And...
你一定是纳文
You must be Naveen.
你好呀钦图，我上次在穿线仪式上见过你
How are you 'chintu'? I saw you at the threading ceremony, last.
不是钦图
Not 'chintu'.
地下城主
Dungeon Master.
在地下城和主人之间有一个下划线
There's an underscore between Dungeon and Master.
所以..
So...
你们想让我为你们公司工作
You guys want me to work for your company.
你跟他讲
You tell him.
我们有兴趣讨论一下..
We were interested in discussing the possibilities...
我研究了你的想法
I looked into your idea.
其实挺有意思的
It's... quite interesting actually.
研究过了吗？
Looked into?
但是，到目前为止，我还没有给你发过邮件
But, I haven't sent you any mail, as yet!
但是你已经给 NASSCOM 发过了，不是吗？
But you'd mailed NASSCOM, hadn't you?
你看..
You see...
邮件隐私是个神话，我的朋友
Privacy on mail is a myth my friend!
所以... 如果我加入你们..
So... If I join you guys...
我有什么好处
How do I benefit?
我能得到什么？
What do I get?
机会
Opportunity!
当然，一开始也会有一笔津贴
Of course, there'll also be a stipend initially.
大约... 7千块
About... 7K.
8... 8千
8... 8K. Yeah.
随着我们公司的发展，你们的工资也会增加
And as we grow, your monetory compensation will obviously increase...
你知道国际反恐精英大赛的奖金是多少吗？
Do you know what's the prize money for the Internation Counter Strike competition?
多少钱？
How much?
475,000...
美元
Dollars.
4... 4乘以6等于24..
4... 4 times 6 is 24...
你赢了？
And you won that?
两次
Twice!
4... 4乘2等于8... 8乘6等于48..
4... 4 times 2 is 8... 8 times 6 is 48...
所以理论上来说... 我可以雇佣你们
So theoritically... I can hire you guys.
而不是你雇佣我
But not the other way round.
我要30% 的股权
I want 30% equity...
还有... 否决产品设计
And... veto on product design.
Dungeon_master@hotmail.com
不要忘记下划线
Don't forget the underscore.
星期一之前给我发邮件
Mail me by Monday.
或者把它保存在你的草稿中
Or just save it in your drafts.
我会看的
I'll read it.
我想我们需要杰图
I think we need Jeetu.
你认为我们需要杰图吗？
Do you think we need Jeetu?
我们需要杰图
We need Jeetu.
我们必须先更改所有账户的密码
We'll have to first change the passwords for all our accounts.
怎么了，创业者？
What's up, start-up founder?
谈完这笔交易后，你们的电池看起来没电了
Your battery looks dead after listeninig to the deal.
怎么了，企业家叔叔？
What's up, entrepreneur uncle?
给我们也分一些股份吧
Pass on some stake to us as well!
听着，杰图，没有别的出路了，你必须加入进来
Listen up Jeetu. There's no other way out. You have to join in.
我不能参加了
I can't join in.
对不起
Sorry.
我告诉过你
I told you!
你永远不能说服一个跟你上床的女人
You can never convince a woman who gives you sex!
不
Noo!
桑亚已经同意了
Suamya has agreed.
所以呢？
SO?
哦
Ohh!
什么？
What?
你有没有试着和他谈谈？
Did you try talking to him?
这就是我从一岁半开始一直想做的事情
That's all I've been able to do since I was 1.5 years old. TRY to talk!
和谁？
With whom?
你没看过《乌丹》吗？
Haven't you watched 'Udaan'?
哦
Ohhhh!
你爸爸？
Your dad?
他酗酒？
He's alcoholic?
他不是酒鬼..
He's not alcoholic...
你为什么害怕你爸爸? 你还是个孩子吗？
Why are you scared of your dad? Are you still a kid?
纳文，我的存折都在他那里
Naveen. Even my passbook is with him.
如果下个月一号我的工资还没有到账
If my salary doesn't get credited on the 1st of the next month...
我就得用命来顶
My life will get debited.
你们先开始吧
You guys, atleast, start.
我会试着每天下班后投入几个小时的工作
I'll see. I'll try putting in a couple of hours of work, everyday after my job.
”你们先做””我等等看”你疯了吗？
"You guys start", "I'll see". Are you mad?
这样的话，即使是测试版6个月之内也做不好
This way, even the Beta version won't be ready in 6 months.
还有很多事情要做
There's so much to do.
不好意思
Excuse me!
这不是印度历史上最酷的公司吗？
Aren't you the guys launching the coolest company of Indian history?
嘿! 创业的太太来了-嘿
Hey! The start-up wags are here. -Hey!
那些拜金主义者甚至比钱还早到这里
The gold-diggers are here even before the money.
听着，你需要一个更好的首席执行官
Listen, you need to get a better CEO, though!
不知道是不是最酷的，但肯定是最短命的
Don't know about the coolest, but could be most short-lived for sure!
不要在这样的好日子里说丧气话，杰图
Don't say such bad things on a good day like this, Jeetu.
这是给你的
This is for you'll.
怎么了，杰图？
So what's up, Jeetu?
你在这儿干什么？
What are you doing here?
我是来面试的
I've come here for the interview!
曼达尔，那只是个玩笑，不会有面试的
Mandal, that was only a joke. There's no interview happening.
我知道，我知道
I know. I know.
我懂笑话
I know jokes.
我上了一个月的即兴喜剧课
I've taken improv. comedy classes for a month.
这有人吗?-有
Is this taken? -Yes.
好的
OK!
你还不明白吗，混蛋？
Don't you get it, motherf**ker?
我们的电池没电了
Anyway our battery's down...
这是我们的事，曼达尔
This is our shit, Madal!
我们不需要你
We don't need you.
相信我
Trust me.
你需要我
You need me!
事实上没有我..
Infact without me...
你没有公司
You don't have a company!
好吧，去拿把椅子来
OK, go get a chair.
我们现在面试你
We'll interview you right away!
听他把话说完，就一次
Just hear him out na, once.
告诉我
Tell me.
我们为什么要雇佣你？
Why should we hire you?
作为一个工商管理硕士
You know, as an MBA...
我一直对我的角色与责任很清楚
I've always had a clarity about my R&Rs.
我的一个主要关键领域出了问题..
One of my KRA has been problem...
我们不需要市场经理，我们需要一个程序员..
We don't need a marketing manager. We need a coder...
谢谢你的申请，面试结束
Thanks for applying. You interview's over.
不不不等一下
No. No. No. One second.
我可以解决你的问题
I can solve your problem.
我可以给你一些你需要的东西
I can give you something, which you need.
我可以给你杰图
I can give you Jeetu!
怎么做？
How?
现阶段，你不会得到任何投资..
Till the time, you'll don't get an investment...
由我来付杰图的工资
I'll pay for Jeetu's salary.
一部分是我的工资，另一部分是我的积蓄
A part of it through my salary and a part through my savings.
但我保证，杰图现在的工资是多少，我就给他多少
But I'll ensure that, Jeetu keeps getting as much as he gets from his company.
曼达尔你为什么要为我们做这些事？
Mandal. Why would you do these things for us?
不是为你们
Not for you guys...
我是为了我自己
I'll do it for myself!
你们是我最好的朋友
You guys are the best friends I've ever had.
我知道除了纳文
I know, apart from Naveen...
我们并没有很多交流的机会
We've not interacted as much...
但是我一直认为，我们四个是一个非常好的团队
But I've always thought, that the four of us are a very good team.
当我看《人只活一次》的时候
You know when I'd seen 'Zindagi Milegi Na Dobara'
我决定..
I'd decided that...
我们四个也是，就像电影主角一样……
The four of us too, just like them...
开创一番事业
Would go on a trip.
但是主角只有3个人
But ZNMD had only 3 guys.
好吧，那么... 就三个主角
OK. Then... like 'Dil Chahta Hai'.
再说一次，只有三个人，曼达尔
Again, only 3 guys, Mandal.
摇滚乐队肯定有4个人
'Rock On' definitely had 4 guys.
第四个得了癌症死了，只剩下三个
The 4th one, gets cancer and dies. Only 3 remain.
重点是如果我加入你们的初创公司
The point is, if I join your start-up...
这样杰图就可以全职和我们一起工作了
Then Jeetu can work full-time with us.
不是所有的MBA都那么糟糕
All MBAs... are not that bad.
那么……
Soo...
有人要说什么吗，还是我们就这样坐一个小时？
Is somebody going to say something, or are we sitting just like this for the next hour?
别担心，伙计们
Don't worry, guys.
不会那么糟的
It won't be that bad.
后街男孩... 欧耶
Backstreet Boys... Alright!
干杯
Cheers!
我们有四个人啦
And then there were four!
干杯! 干杯! 干杯
Cheers! Cheers! Cheers!
终于，他让自己变得有用了
Finally, he's made himself useful!
好了，杰图回来了
So, Jeetu's back!
最重要的一点 -这个消息不能从这里传出去
Important point - This news doesn't get out of here!
如果爸爸知道了... - 别再说什么”爸爸爸爸”了
If dad gets to know... - Stop going "Dad. Dad."
一旦我们成为价值百万美元的公司，你爸爸也会冷静下来的
Once we're a million dollar company, even your dad will chill out!
此外，我还做了一些研究，为我们的公司想了几个名字
And also, I've done some research and thought of a few names for our compnay.
我想，我们公司的名字里应该有‘ le’
I think, our compnay name should have 'le' in it!
就像Google，Apple，Oracle
Like Google had 'gle', Apple has 'ple', Oracle has 'cle'
你在胡说些什么? 你又开始用你那愚蠢的营销逻辑了
What non-sense are you talking? You've started with your stupid marketing logics again!
请不要往我身上扔薯条，我是市场部经理
Please don't throw fries on me. I'm the marketing manager!
对不起
Oops! Sorry.
喂！为什么要扔我
Careful! Why are you throwing it on me?
这就是你的百万美元团队？
So, this is your million dollar team?
恭喜
Congrats